- They are not.
- They are too.
(Leonard:)Your hypothesis is completely disconfirmed
by all the data.
(Leonard:)You're just clinging to it
out of intellectual stubbornness.
(Raj:)No, you're displaying a shocking ignorance
of the subject matter.
(Raj:)Mummies and zombies
are the exact same thing.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah?
(Leonard:)Mummies are wrapped in bandages.
(Raj:)That's called a fashion choice.
(Leonard:)All right. You brought this on yourself.
(Leonard:)- Sheldon, get him.
- Lf a zombie bites you...
(Sheldon:)...you turn into a zombie.
(Sheldon:)However, if a mummy bites you...
(Sheldon:)...all you turn into
is some schmo with a mummy bite.
(Sheldon:)So, like a zombie that's been eaten
from the waist down...
(Sheldon:)...you, sir, have no leg to stand on.
- Good boy. Here's a cookie.
- Oh, thank you.
(Howard:)Hey, fellas, what's going on?
(Leonard:)Mummies and zombies again.
Ahh. They're not the same thing.
(Leonard:)You get a cookie too.
(Howard:)Thanks.
(Howard:)Guess who picked up his new car
this morning.